bearchive.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy – BotComics

Our Privacy Policy is designed to inform you of how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and assist you when making decisions regarding the use of our site and our products and services.

**What information do we collect?**

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name, but not the e-mail address. We collect the e-mail addresses of those who post messages to our forum and payment information when signing up for our ´members site´ (e.g., credit card number, e-mail address and billing address).

We will offer a free electronic newsletter to users. Our company gathers the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by following the link provided in every newsletter that points users to the subscription management page. Users can also subscribe to the newsletters at the time of registration.

We may offer interactive polls to users so they can easily share their opinions with other users and see what our audience thinks about important issues. Opinions or other responses to polls are aggregated and are not identifiable to any particular user.

We use cookies to store visitor's preferences, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site.

**Uses**

The information we collect is used for internal review, customer service inquiries, enhancing the user experience (keeping accounts logged in, thus eliminating the need to sign in on each visit), as well as using a cookie system to "tag" users after they have voted on polls, so they can vote only once on a particular question (this tag is not correlated with information about individual users).

We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies.

When we use third parties to assist us in processing your personal information (such as CCBill), we require that they comply with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

We may also share information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services.  
Cofidentiality and security

We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.  
Your choices

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases) that we maintain about them, as well as a description of information that we maintain about them (only after appropriate identity is confirmed).

You may decline to provide us with optional user information and/or refuse cookies in your browser, though many features of the site will cease to function properly as a result.
